Okay, I'll stop!
(Raj:)Hello?
(Raj:)Hey, so, listen, Claire,
change of plans...
(Claire:)Fine. Do what you want,
but she's playing you.
(Raj:)I don't think so.
She sounded pretty upset.
(Claire:)You mean like...
“I was just really
looking forward to seeing you.
I'm having such a rough day.”
(Raj:)Emily, listen...
(Raj:)I'm sorry,
(Raj:)but I can't come by.
(Emily:)Why not?
(Raj:)I think we both know
if I come over,
(Raj:)we're gonna get back together and...
I told you
(Emily:)I needed a friend.
(Leonard:)What do you think
is happening here?
(Raj:)Call you right back.
The-the revisions I made
start on page four.
(Penny:)Wow. That is a lot
of “whereupons”.
(Amy:)You should see the
Valentine's Day card he gave me.
“Article three:
As it pertains to this project,
“Dr. Sheldon Cooper promises
to abstain from all insulting or